This is Hanane, a panda. This is Rurun-chan the panda. Hello, I am Rurun-chan the panda. Hello panda.
I'm a panda. What do you do in this panda outfit? Today we will play Othello.
Let's play black and white.
Then, whichever you like. Then, let's go ahead and play black, please.
Cut.
Cool. This time, you know, why am I dressed as a panda? We are a unit station.
We will be doing a song called Mr. Panda. Yay. I'm so happy.
It's an idol song, right? Yes, it is.
And I'm so happy to be able to work with them.
It's a good fit for me too. I can see why.
I like Risa-chan's song a lot.
I love it. Karen says she's glad she's an idol too.
Karen's dance teacher told her to sing the first A melody, and I wish Karen could hear it from Rin-chan.
I guess so. I'm like myself.
Today, too, in the second number, I was like, "I admire you, Karen. She told me that.
You said that I have something that you don't have. You said that.
I have to be in sync with him. It's difficult, isn't it?
There will be calls and things like that, so I hope you'll watch. I'm really looking forward to that.
Isn't that the call you've been longing for? Yes, it is.
I had them do it at the Centante or something, so I really longed for it.
There must be songs that are loved by everyone. Yes, I'm sure.
I'm looking forward to seeing other people's songs. It's great, isn't it? Other people's songs, too. Each one.
Do you have a favorite lyric, Kana-san? I'm pretty sure I just said it myself.
I like the story. Ah, yes, yes.
Like a change of feelings. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Is there?
Acal has twintails. I made a wish. It's cute. Certainly.
I like it. Twin-tail hair is what we wish for, right? We do.
Wow.
At first I wondered what kind of song it was, since you said "Panda". I wondered what kind of song it would be.
When I heard that it was going to be just the two of us, I thought it would be a little too "puri-puri" or something, but it turned out to be really hot.
Like an emo idol. It's emo.
I knew it. Fighter wrote it for me. It's cute. Cute.
Panda.
I like the choreography too.
The choreography is good, isn't it?
How about the hand gestures? When I asked them how they liked the hand movements, they said, "Is it OK to dance to this song any way you want?
I was told that it's okay to be different.
It's not so much about matching, but more about imagining each idol's image.
It was amazing, wasn't it? It was the first time I was told that.
It's amazing. I'm almost ready to get a vote.
Tetsuchan.
It's now black and white.
It's done.
So, I'll take 18.
Forty-six.
Lungpanda wins.
Touch Panda.
Touch Panda
And now, there is a penalty game.
I don't know how to say this, but...
The winner has to dance to the call of Panda's song.
The winner dances to the call.
And the loser has to say the call
It's a game of punishment.
But this is because I really want you to say the call.
I want you to say it.
When it's coming down the line.
I want you to say it like that.
I want you to say it.
I'd like to show you a model of the call in the next video.
I would be very happy if you could do it at the live performance.
Okay, I'd like to do it now.
Okay, so now that we are ready, I would like to do the call.
Yes, I'm ready to do the call.
I will say the call that I want you to do, and I would be very happy if you could say this call at the live performance.
Yes.
Runchan will dance for us.
I will dance. Yay.
Then, let's go.
Yes, let's go.
Let's start the music!
♪ Karen
I have something to say!
I knew it! Karen is cute!
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you!
I finally found my princess!
The reason I was born!
It's to meet the light!
Come live your life with me!
I love you more than anything in the world!
I love you!
Even though
I would be happy if you conveyed your love in this way.
It would make me happy, wouldn't it?
Yes, it would. That's what I'm talking about.
Well, I kind of thought to myself that Karen is cute,
In a manner of speaking, yes, I would be happy if you put it in the swathe and say so.
So, Mr. Kanda, I am looking forward to working with you to make this a wonderful song,
Please look forward to the performance.
I am Reki.
I'm Reki.
I'm Reki!
So, that was the two Kandasan!
Thank you very much!
Bye bye!
We can't wait to go out and play.
Yes, we want to go!
We haven't been there once in 8 years.
That's right!